NAZME AIMAN

SOFWARE ENGINEER



- - 6011-37064729
- \bigvee
- nazmeaimanyunus@gmail.com
- 0
- Sungai Buloh, Selangor, Malaysia



https://www.nazmeaiman.tech/

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE

- PHP
- JAVASCRIPT
- SQL

LIBRARIES / FRAMEWORK

- LARAVEL
- LARAVEL FORGE
- VUE JS
- REACT NATIVE
- CAPACITOR
- QUASAR
- TAILWIND CSS

EDUCATION

BACHERLOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (BUSINESS COMPUTING)

(UITM SHAH ALAM)

2014 - 2020

CGPA: 3.37

DIPLOMA OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

(UITM RAUB PAHANG)

2014 - 2016

CGPA: 3.03

PROFILE

My name is Nazme Aiman bin Yunus, 25 years old, a full stack engineer. I have a diploma in Computer Science and a Bachelor's Degree of Information Technology majoring in Business Computing. I have 2 years of experiences in sofware engineering field.

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK ENGINEER

Freelancer (Go-Tadika)

2021 - currently

- Handling backend and frontend.
- · Programming language: PHP, Javascript, SQL
- Programming libraries / Framework: Laravel / Laravel Forge / Vue Js
 / Capacitor/ React Native / Quasar / Vuetify.
- Code versioning control: GIT

JUNIOR SOFWARE ENGINEER

Encore Med Sdn. Bhd

2020 - 2021

- · Handling backend API.
- Handling some module of front-end.
- Programming language: PHP, Javascript, SQL
- Programming libraries / Framework: Backbone JS/ Vue Js / Cordova / Jquery
- Code versioning control: SVN

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

S.M.K BUKIT GADING 2010 - 2014

SPM: 4A 4B 1C

CERTIFICATES

ORACLES DATABASE CERTIFICATION

05 / 2018

ALI BABA
CERTIFICATION

06 / 2019

EXPERIENCE

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER (INTERNSHIP)

WRO International

2020

- Develop and maintaining client website.
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Programming libraries / Framework: Wordpress

IT SUPPORT (INTERNSHIP)

Open Soft Technologies 2007

• Website design (HTML)

- Working in a support team.

LANGUAGES

- BAHASA (NATIVE LANGUAGES)
- ENGLISH (PROFESIONAL PROFIENCY)

REFERENCES

MADAM WAN AMALINA BINTI WAN HARIRI

SuperVisor Final Year Project

Email: amalina@fskm.uitm.edu.my

DR. NORJANSALIKA BINTI JANOM

ACADEMIC ADVISOR

Email: norjan@fskm.uitm.edu.my